Guide to the Jimmy De Sana Papers 1954-1997 (bulk 1977-1990) MSS.202
Fales Library and Special Collections
Jimmy De Sana Papers
1954-1997
1977-1990
Fales Library and Special Collections
Pat Hearn Gallery
De Sana, Jimmy
MSS.202
31 Linear Feet (79 boxes)
The Jimmy De Sana papers provide documentation of De Sana's career as an artist and commercial photographer. The collection consists of photographic prints, slides, negatives, clippings, posters, reviews, and photographic equipment and other objects. The bulk of the material covers 1977-1990, although the collection spans the mid 1950s-1997.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
As of 23 February 2010, Series III - VIII are on loan and unavailable for research.
Provenance
The Jimmy De Sana Papers were donated to the Fales Library by Laurie Simmons, executor of the Jimmy De Sana Trust, in 2008.
Arrangement note
The collection has been arranged into 15 series. Series III through VIII (slides and negatives) are currently unavailable to researchers.
Series I:Photographic Prints organized by project
Subseries A: Silver gelatin prints from "101 Nudes"
Subseries B: Silver gelatin prints associated with the 1980 book Submission.
Subseries C: Cibachrome and color c-prints from the "Early Sex" project
Subseries D: Photographic prints from the "$bfat" project
Subseries E: Photographic prints from the "$dobjects" project
Subseries F: Photographic prints from the "Auto-Portraits" project
Subseries G: Photographic prints from the Salvation book project
Series II: Photographic Prints organized by theme
Subseries A: Photographic prints from Early Work theme
Subseries B: Photographic prints from Events theme
Subseries C: Photographic prints from Landscape theme
Subseries D: Photographic prints from the Paper Collage theme
Subseries E: Photographic prints from the Portrait theme
Subseries F: Photographic prints from the Miscellaneous theme
Subseries G: Photographic prints from Other Artists' Work theme
Series III: Color Transparency Slides organized by project
Subseries A: Slides from the Submission project
Subseries B: Slides from the "Early Sex" project
Subseries C: Slides from the "$bfat" project
Subseries D: Slides from the "$dobjects" project
Subseries E: Slides from the "Auto-Portrait" project
Subseries F: Slides from the "Cut Up" project
Subseries G: Slides from the Salvation project
Series IV:Color Transparency Slides organized by theme
Subseries A: Slides from the Documentation theme
Subseries B: Slides from the Events theme
Subseries C: Slides from the Landscape theme
Subseries D: Slides from the Miscellaneous theme
Subseries E: Slides shot from the film "O'Hara's Wife"
Subseries F: Slides from the Paper Collage theme
Subseries G: Slides from the Portrait theme
Subseries H: Slides from the Travel theme
Series V: Silver Gelatin Negative Film organized by project
Subseries A: Negatives from the "101 Nudes" project
Subseries B: Negatives from the Submission project
Subseries C: Negatives from the "Early Sex" project
Subseries D: Negatives from the "$bfat" project
Subseries E: Negatives from the "$dobjects" project
Subseries F: Negatives from the "Cut Up" project
Subseries G: Negatives from the "Auto-Portrait" project
Series VI:Silver Gelatin Negative Film organized by theme
Subseries A: Negatives from the Documentation theme
Subseries B: Negatives from the Early Work theme
Subseries C: Negatives from the Events theme
Subseries D: Negatives from the Landscape theme
Subseries E: Negatives from the Miscellaneous theme
Subseries F: Negatives from the Nudes theme
Subseries G: Negatives from the Paper Collage theme
Subseries H: Negatives from the Portraits theme
Subseries I: Negatives from the Reproductions of Other Artists' Work theme
Subseries J: Negatives from the Travel theme
Subseries K: Medium-format Negatives
Sub-subseries i: Negatives from the Documentation theme
Sub-subseries ii: Negatives from the Miscellaneous theme
Sub-subseries iii: Negatives from the Portrait theme
Sub-subseries iv: Negatives from the Reproductions of Other Artists' Work theme
Series VII: Color Negative Film organized by project
Subseries A: Negatives from the Submission project
Subseries B: Negatives from the "Early Sex" project
Series VIII: Color Negative Film organized by theme
Subseries A: Negatives from the Landscape theme
Subseries B: Negatives from the Miscellaneous theme
Subseries C: Negatives from the Reproductions of Other Artists' Work theme
Subseries D: Negatives from the Portraits theme
Series IX: Half-tone triplicate reproductions organized by project
Subseries A: Half-tone 8 X 10s from the Salvation project
Series X:Silver Gelatin Contact Sheets organized by project
Subseries A: Contact sheets from the "101 Nudes" project
Subseries B: Contact sheets from the Submission project
Subseries C: Contact sheets from the "$bfat" project
Subseries D: Contact sheets from the "$dobjects" project
Subseries E: Contact sheets from the "Auto-Portrait" project
Subseries F: Contact sheets from the "Cut Up" project
Subseries G: Contact sheets from the Salvation project
Series XI: Silver Gelatin Contact Sheets organized by theme
Subseries A: Contact sheets from the Events theme
Subseries B: Contact sheets from the Landscape theme
Subseries C: Contact sheets from the Miscellaneous theme
Subseries D: Contact sheets from the Portrait theme
Subseries E: Contact sheets from the Reproductions of Other Artists' Work theme
Subseries F: Contact sheets from the Travel theme
Series XII:Pat Hearn Materials
Subseries A: Color Transparency Slides documentation of projects and installations
Subseries B: Papers and clippings collected by Pat Hearn Gallery
Series XIII: Ephemera
Subseries A: Papers and clippings found throughout the Jimmy De Sana estate
Subseries B: Papers and clippings compiled by Jimmy De Sana
Series XIV: Objects
Series XV: Media
Subseries A: Access Copies
Subseries B: Originals
Subseries C: VHS tapes
Oversize Series II: Oversize Photographic Prints organized by theme
Subseries E: Portrait
Subseries F: Miscellaneous
Oversize Series XIII: Ephemera
Subseries A: Papers and clippings found throughout the Jimmy De Sana estate
Subseries B: Papers and clippings compiled by Jimmy De Sana
Series Arrangement
Series I: Prints by Project
Series II: Prints by Theme
Series III: Slides by Project
Series IV: Slides by Theme
Series V: Negative by Project
Series VI: Negatives by Theme
Series VII: Color Negative by Project
Series VIII: Color Negatives by Theme
Series IX: Half-tone Triplicate Redproductions by Project
Series X: Silver Gelatin Contact Sheets by Project
Series XI: Silver Gelatin Contact Sheets by Theme
Series XII: Pat Hearn Materials
Series XIII: Ephemera
Series XIV: Objects
Series XV: Media
Oversize - Series II: Photographic Prints by Theme
Oversize - Series XIII: Ephemera; Clippings, Reproductions, Advertisements
Biographical Note
Jimmy De Sana was born in Detroit on November 12, 1949, where he lived until his family relocated to Atlanta in 1955. De Sana studied art in high school and at the University of Georgia in Atlanta. In 1972, before moving to New York City, he published 101 Nudes, a lithographic portfolio. This first mature work, comprised of nude photographs of himself and his friends in suburban settings, introduced themes that remained important throughout his career.
De Sana's first exhibition took place in 1979 at the Stefanotti Gallery on West 57th Street. A visible figure in the East Village art scene of the 1970s and 1980s, he participated in the "Times Square Show", "New York/New Wave" and was a frequent contributor to FILE Magazine, SoHo News, the Village Voice, Bomb and New York Rocker. He self-published a book of photographs, Submission, in 1980, which includes an introduction by William S. Burroughs. Though his career lasted less than two decades, De Sana produced work in a variety of styles. He used unconventional processes and techniques including negative prints, double exposures, and vividly colored lighting.
At the time of his death, De Sana was working on a book of photographic collages, made largely in the darkroom, constructed of images of mundane household objects. The book, Salvation, remains incomplete. De Sana was represented by Pat Hearn Gallery from 1987 (posthumously) through 1997. De Sana died of AIDS in New York City in 1990. He was forty years old. His work continues to be shown internationally.
Sources:
Bourdon, David. "Jimmy De Sana at Pat Hearn." Art in America, November, 1995
Scope and Content Note
The Jimmy De Sana Papers, which exceeds 25,000 items, consist of comprehensive documentation of Jimmy De Sana's career as an artist and commercial photographer. Materials include photographic prints, slides, negatives, clippings, posters, reviews, and photographic equipment and other objects. The materials span the mid 1950s–1997 with the bulk of the material covering 1977–1990.
The bulk of the collection is made up of photographic materials, which have been separated into eleven series according to type (prints, color transparency slides, silver gelatin negative film, color negative film, half-tone reproductions, and silver gelatin contact sheets) and project or theme. What constitutes a "project" was based on exhibition records and documentation in the press.
Project Titles and Dates:
101 Nudes, 1972
Submission circa 1978-1980
Early Sex, circa 1979 – 1983 (Also labeled by Jimmy DeSana "Greenwich Sex" and "Sex")
$bfat, circa 1983 – 1984 (also labeled by Jimmy DeSana "Fat")
$dobjects, circa 1984 – 1987 (Also labeled by Jimmy DeSana " Early Collage" and "Early Abstract")
Auto-Portraits, circa 1984 – 1985
Cut Ups, circa 1985 – 1986
Salvation, circa 1986 - 1991
When there are no materials corresponding to a particular project in a given series, that project is skipped in the sequence.
"Themes" have been identified by labels existing within the estate or by visual similarity. Annotations or labels that were written by Jimmy De Sana are indicated in the item descriptions by his initials(JDS). When there are no materials corresponding to a particular theme in a given series, that theme is skipped in the sequence.
Theme Titles:
Documentation
Early Work
Events
Landscape
Miscellaneous
Nudes
"O'Hara's Wife"
Paper Collage
Portrait
Reproductions of Other Artists' Work
Travel
Series VI Subseries K contains medium format negatives which could not be integrated into the storage binders with the rest of the material because of size. Subseries K is stored separately, but organized into sub-subseries which match themes elsewhere in Series VI and should be considered of a piece with them.
When an item is listed in the finding aid with a box number, but no folder number, it indicates that the item is stored in an archival photo binder box. Throughout the collection, for materials housed in binders, a labeled sheet of paper has been inserted to indicate when a new subseries begins. Works not titled by Jimmy De Sana himself appear as "Title:______" in the finding aid.
Separated Materials
Negatives and slides (Series III,IV,V,VI,VII,VIII) have been termporarily removed from the collection for use by the donor.
Photography, Artistic.; Photography |x Exhibitions |z New York (State) |z New York.; Photographic prints.; Black-and-white photographs.; Negatives (photographic); Photographers -- United States.; Color photographs.; Tear sheets.; Record covers.; Portrait photography.; Portrait Photography |z United States.; Portrait prints |y 20th century.; Résumés (personnel records); Slides (photographs); Gay men -- United States.; Contact sheets.; Printed ephemera.; Reviews (document genre); Fliers (printed matter); AIDS (Disease) and art -- United States.; Art, American -- New York (State) -- 20th century.; Black-and-white negatives.; Photographs.; Color negatives.; Color slides.; Cover Art.; Downtown Collection.; Exhibition catalogs.; Photography |v Exhibitions.; Photography |z United States.; Giorno, John; Dlugos, Tim; Sellers, Terence; Hannah, Duncan; Bourdon, David; Stefanotti, Robert, 1947-; McCormick, Carlo; Grief, Paula; Idol, Billy; Churikova, Inna; Pat Hearn Gallery; Harry, Debbie; Paik, Nam June, 1932-2006; Warhol, Andy, 1928-1987; Burroughs, William S., 1914-1997; Anger, Kenneth; Astor, Patti; Bidlo, Mike; Lindsay, Arto; White, James Chance, 1953-; Anderson, Laurie, 1947-; Simmons, Laurie; Smith, Rupert; Hell, Richard; Cage, John; Acconci, Vito, 1940-; Dali, Salvador, 1904-1989; Curtis, Jackie, 1947-1985; Battcock, Gregory, 1937-; Smith, Patti; Cote, Thom; Acker, Kathy, 1948-1997; Cortez, Diego; Nudeback, Gail; Mitchell, Eric; Byrne, David, 1952-; Ono, Yōko; Johnson, Ray, 1927-1995; Eno, Brian, 1948-; Brecht, George; Cutrone, Ronnie
- Series I: Prints by project
  Scope and Content note
  Photographs without titles are listed as "Title:_____".
  - Subseries A: 101 Nudes
    Scope and Contents note
    All prints are 8x10
    - Title:, 1972 (Box 1)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Description: Byron on bed
      Process: Silver Gelatin
      Number of Items: 1
    - Title:, 1972 (Box 1)
      Description: Gail Nudeback
      Process:
      Number of Items: 5
  - Subseries B: Submission
    Items in subseries B are organized to reflect the organization of the De Sana's published book Submission; items from the project that were not included in the final publication are included at the end of the series. Items from the Salvation project are organized to correspond with their appearance in the proposed publication. All prints are 8x10.
    - Title: Dog, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
      Description:
    - Title: Panty Hose, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Contact Paper, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: String, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Erection, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Toilet, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Carpet, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Shower, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Rubber Tube, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Bathtub [Titled 'Enema' in the published book], 1977 (Box 1)
    - Title: Enema [Titled 'Bathtub' in the published book], 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Jock Strap, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Coffee Table, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Whip, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Giant Dildo, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Television, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Terrace, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Refrigerator (Box 1)
    - Title: Kitchen, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Dildo, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Cat, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Dog, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Egg, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Lamp, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Masking Tape, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Condom, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Pliers, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Title: Sofa, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Title:, 1978 - 1979 (Box 1)
      Description: Woman wearing mask, Does not appear in the published book
    - Title:, 1978 - 1979 (Box 1)
      Description: woman wearing mask in profile, Does not appear in the published book
    - Title:, 1978 - 1979 (Box 1)
      Description: Woman with T.V., Does not appear in the published book
  - Subseries C: Early Sex
    Box 2 is an oversized flat box.
    - Title: (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Description: Pool
      Process: Polaroid photograph
    - Title: Auto, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Title: Auto, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Process: 16x111/2 Color C-Print
    - Title: Shoe, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Process: 16x11 1/2 Color C-Print
    - Title: Plastic Wrap, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Description: Outdoor plastic bag
      Process: 8x10 Silver Gelatin
    - Title:, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Description: Coat Hanger
      Number of Items: 2
  - Subseries D: $bfat
    Box 2 is an oversized flat box. Prints are 8x10 or 16x20.
    - Title: Bubblegum (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Title: Cowboy Hat (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Title: (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Description: Sweatshirt twins
      Number of Items: 3
    - Title: (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Description: Twins, big feet
      Process: Cibachrome
    - Title: Pants, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Description: Twins
      Process: 16x20 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: Pants, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Description: Pants
    - Title: Pants, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Subseries E: $dobjects
    - Title:, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Description: Abstract
    - Title:, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Description: Abstract with Wooden "O"
    - Title: Ketchup and Mustard, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Description: Dalmatian Ketchup and Mustard
      Process: 11x14 Cibachrome
    - Title: Samples, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Description: Fabric, wood "O"
    - Title: Pipe Cleaner, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Description: Spiral brown drops yellow field
    - Title:, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Description: "Pyramid" or "Softball"
    - Title:, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Description: Mandarines
      Process: 8x10 Cibachrome
    - Title: Easter Chicks, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Description: Peeps
    - Title: Popcorn, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Description: Popcorn loops
    - Title:, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Description: Vegetables
      Process: 5x10 Cibachrome
    - Title:, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Process: 11x14 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: Popcorn, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Title:, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Description: String Abstraction
    - Title:, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Subseries F: Auto-Portrait
    Box 3 is an oversized flat box.
    - Title: Cellophane Tape, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Title: Cellophane Tape, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Title: Smoke, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Description: or "Smoke Cowboy"
    - Title: Aluminum Foil, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Title: Party Picks, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Description: Tooth Picks
      Process: 4x6 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: Stitches, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Description: Stitches
      Process: 15x20 Cibachrome
    - Title:, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Description: Nude Blue arm drips
    - Title:, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Description: Pizza Crust
  - Subseries G: Salvation
    Items from the Salvation project are organized to correspond with their appearance in the proposed publication. Box 3 is an oversized flat box.
    - Title: Gym Shorts (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Title: Gym Shorts (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Title: Kneeling Magical Figure (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Description: de Sana cover
      Process: 8x10 Color C-Print
    - Title: Parka (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Title: Parka (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Process: 4x5 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Description: Figure oval - gym shorts
    - Title: Coconut (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Series II: Prints by theme
  Themes have been identified by labels existing within the estate or by visual similarity. Annotations or labels that were written by Jimmy De Sana are indicated in the item description by his initials (JDS).
  Items from the Portrait theme are organized alphabetically by the subject's last name. Where a last name is absent slides are organized alphabetically by first name. These are followed by unidentified subjects.
  - Subseries A: Early Work
    Box 4 is an oversized flat box.
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 17)
      Description: Nude in bathtub
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 18)
      Description: Poodle
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 18)
      Description: Viking
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 18)
      Description: Dark image
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 19)
      Description: Hotel room
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 19)
      Description: Pet
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 19)
      Description: Store Window
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 20)
      Description: Fruit market
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 20)
      Description: Child
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 20)
      Description: Rural
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 21)
      Description: Portraits of Men
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 22)
      Description: Portrait of a Man
      Process: 7x9 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 22)
      Description: Portrait of a Woman
      Process: 5x8 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 22)
      Description: Woman on the street
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 23)
      Process: 6x8 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 23)
      Description: Portrait of Street Portrait of Woman
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 23)
      Description: Robert Steffanotty's mother's trees
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 25)
      Process: 9x13 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Title: (Box 4, Folder 27)
      Description: Palm Tree and Sky
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Portrait of a couple on the street
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Portrait of a woman on the street
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Building Face
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: House at night
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: People on the street
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Sign with manequin heads
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Fanny May Candy Store
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Nativity Scene
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Trees in the dark
      Number of Items: 8
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Car at night
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Night scene
      Process: 6x9 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Number of Items: 4
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Beauty School
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Milk Carton
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Snowman
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Dutch Treat Coffee Shop
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Snow scene hand tinted
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: House at night hand tinted
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Telephone wire
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Street scene
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Grand piano
    - Title: (Box 5)
      Description: Round mirror
  - Subseries B: Events
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Jimmy de Sana and Diego Cortez - documentation of photographic portraits at PS 1
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: "Arraignment"
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Interior
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Fountain with photographer
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Mannequin at night
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Shoes
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Musicians
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Dogs
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Bleecker Bob's
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Blurred nude
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Blurred face
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Man in hat
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Man in sweater, face covered
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Dinner party
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Street scene at night
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Speaker at podium
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Parking meter
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Fountain at night
    - Title: (Box 6)